{
  "1": {
    "question": "Vanilla or chocolate?",
    "answers": ["Vanilla", "Chocolate"]
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "Pineapple on pizza?",
    "answers": ["Of course! What else?", "Yuck, never in a million years"]
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "Eat or drink soup?",
    "answers": [
      "You EAT the chunks in the soup!",
      "You drink it! Or else it wouldn’t be soup."
    ]
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "Is a hot dog a sandwich?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, it has bread encasing innards",
      "No, it literally has one piece of bread"
    ]
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "What music do you listen to?",
    "answers": [
      "Pop",
      "Country",
      "Rock-and-roll",
      "Classical",
      "What is music?"
    ]
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "What Hogwarts house are you?",
    "answers": [
      "Gryffindor",
      "Syltherin",
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "What is Hogwarts?"
    ]
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "Is it black and blue or white and gold?",
    "answers": [
      "Black and blue",
      "White and gold",
      "I don’t get the reference…"
    ]
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "Did the top stop spinning at the end of Inception?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes! It was all real",
      "No… it’s still fake",
      "What top? What’s Inception?"
    ]
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "In Titanic, could Jack have fit on the door with Rose?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, Rose literally killed Jack!",
      "No, Jack had to sacrifice himself",
      "Who’s Jack and Rose? The Titanic?"
    ]
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "Did James Charles deserve to be canceled?",
    "answers": ["Yes, definitely", "No, it’s unfair", "James Charles, who?"]
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "Which came first: the chicken or the egg?",
    "answers": [
      "The chicken had to lay the egg.",
      "The chicken hatched from the egg.",
      "I really want a fried egg."
    ]
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "Pluto deserves to be a planet.",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, more power to Pluto!",
      "No, clearly not.",
      "Wait, which one is that again?"
    ]
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "Do vegetables feel pain?",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No", "What kind of question is this?"]
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "On an airplane, when sitting in the middle seat, who gets to use the armrests?",
    "answers": [
      "The middle person, of course!",
      "The side person… cause I do it"
    ]
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "If time travel is possible, would we have met time travelers already?",
    "answers": ["Yes, sci-fi in real life", "No, that’s impossible"]
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "Cats or dogs?",
    "answers": ["Cats", "Dogs", "Fish!"]
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "Are you an introvert or an extrovert?",
    "answers": [
      "Introvert",
      "Extroverted introvert",
      "Introverted extrovert",
      "Extrovert"
    ]
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "Have you cried during a Disney movie?",
    "answers": ["Yes, they’re always so sad!", "No, who does?!?"]
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "Do you sing in the shower?",
    "answers": ["Yes, of course! My happy time", "No, what a crazy person…"]
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "What’s the longest amount of time between you dropping something on the floor and picking it up to eat?",
    "answers": ["Never!", "< 5 minutes", "5 - 10 minutes", "Who cares??"]
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "What is your horoscope?",
    "answers": [
      "Don’t know? Have you been living under a rock?!?",
      "Aries",
      "Taurus",
      "Gemini",
      "Cancer",
      "Leo",
      "Virgo",
      "Libra",
      "Scorpio",
      "Sagittarius",
      "Capricorn",
      "Aquarius",
      "Pisces"
    ]
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "MBTI?",
    "answers": [
      "ISTJ",
      "ISFJ",
      "INFJ",
      "INTJ",
      "ISTP",
      "ISFP",
      "INFP",
      "INTP",
      "ESTJ",
      "ESFJ",
      "ENFJ",
      "ENTJ",
      "ESTP",
      "ESFP",
      "ENFP",
      "ENTP"
    ]
  }
}
